export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is 2 + 2?",
    options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 3 + 2?",
    options: ["1", "3", "4", "5"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 4 + 2?",
    options: ["1", "6", "4", "5"],
    correctAnswer: "6",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 3 + 1?",
    options: ["1", "3", "4", "5"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 13 + 2?",
    options: ["15", "13", "24", "35"],
    correctAnswer: "15",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 33 + 22?",
    options: ["51", "33", "44", "55"],
    correctAnswer: "55",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 6 + 2?",
    options: ["1", "8", "4", "5"],
    correctAnswer: "8",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 32 + 24?",
    options: ["51", "53", "56", "35"],
    correctAnswer: "56",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 13 + 12?",
    options: ["11", "13", "14", "15"],
    correctAnswer: "15",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 32 + 22?",
    options: ["15", "63", "45", "54"],
    correctAnswer: "54",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 2 + 7?",
    options: ["1", "3", "4", "9"],
    correctAnswer: "9",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 43 + 25?",
    options: ["61", "63", "68", "65"],
    correctAnswer: "68",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 43 + 62?",
    options: ["101", "103", "105", "108"],
    correctAnswer: "105",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 32 + 82?",
    options: ["111", "113", "114", "115"],
    correctAnswer: "115",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 33 + 12?",
    options: ["41", "23", "45", "35"],
    correctAnswer: "45",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 13 + 22?",
    options: ["41", "43", "44", "45"],
    correctAnswer: "44",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 23 + 20?",
    options: ["12", "30", "43", "50"],
    correctAnswer: "43",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 233 + 203?",
    options: ["436", "430", "443", "450"],
    correctAnswer: "436",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 2 + 0?",
    options: ["5", "2", "3", "1"],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "What is 0.2 + 1.0?",
    options: ["1.2", "1.1", "1.3", "1.4"],
    correctAnswer: "1.2",
  },
];
